Chris Kankiewicz

12231 N 19th Street #264 Phoenix, Arizona 85022 Cell: 602-684-0523

Email: Chris@ChrisKankiewicz.com

AIM: ChrisKankiewicz

Website: www.ChrisKankiewicz.com

Summary

Self taught web designer and programmer with real world experience and a desire to learn. Personal strengths include advanced troubleshooting and problem solving skills, the capacity to acquire and apply new knowledge quickly and great customer service skills.

Experience

Southwest Medical & Rehab

Web Developer (March 2009 - Present)

Conceptualized, designed and implemented detailed e-commerce site layouts

Performed search engine optimizations to enhance traffic to all sites.

Elontec

Systems Technician (October 2007 - February 2008)

Planned and implemented store-wide PC and Point of Sale systems and performed server upgrades.

Performed basic troubleshooting on implemented systems.

PetSmart Store Support Group

Solution Center Technician (February 2008 - March 2009)

Provided over-the-phone technical support to store and corporate employees.

Performed advanced troubleshooting on store servers, registers, and workstations.

Jannenga Enterprises, LLC

Web & Graphics Designer (May 2006 - October 2007)

Conceptualized, designed and coordinated the implementation of detailed web pages and graphics.

Performed routine and advanced maintenance on PC systems, basic and advanced networks, and other digital equipment.

Qualifications

Proficient with:

- PHP
- (X)HTML
- CSS
- · Search Engine Optimization
- Photoshop CS3
- Eclipse IDE
- All Windows operating systems
- · All Microsoft Office applications
- WordPress

Familiar with or learning:

- JavaScript
- Drupal CMS
- · LAMP environments
- MySQL
- Zend IDE
- Java
- · Unix/Linux based operating systems
- Cisco IOS
- Remedy Action Request System

Education

DeVry University

July 2005 - February 2008

• Bachelor's of Science Degree in Network and Communication Management

Shadow Mountain High School

2001 - 2005

- · High school diploma
- · National Honor Society

Achievements

- · Eagle Scout
- Project: CK-Gallery (http://code.web-geek.net/ck-gallery)
- Attended Defcon Security Convention 2005 2008